gearmoose.com 2019-04-06

# PRIVACY | GearMoose

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use aggregated information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please see: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>[  
](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp)

What information do we collect?  
We collect information such as first and last name, and email address from you when you register on our site.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

What do we use your information for?  
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways: 

-To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)  
-To improve our website (we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)  
-To process transactions (Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.)  
-To send periodic emails (The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.)

How do we protect your information?  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

Your Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR):  
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through gearmoose.com or shop.gearmoose.com), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

DATA RETENTION  
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.

Do we use cookies?  
Yes. (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.)  
We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits.

Do we disclose any information to outside parties?  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

Third party links:

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance:

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

Minors:

The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 18.

Your Consent:

By using our site, you consent to our website’s privacy policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy:

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.

Contact Us:

For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection) or by mail using the details provided below:

2288 Gunbarrel Road, STE. 154 PMB 112, Chattanooga, TN, 37421, United States
